A little pause... and we are back.
A little pause...
and we are back.
A little pause... and we are back.
A little pause.
..
and we are back.
Affirmative.
We got a positive ID.
Right.
Lost pet Tora captured.
Mission accomplished.
Oh, my poor little Tora.
Mommy was so worried about her naughty
little fuzzy kids.
Stupid cat.
That kitty deserves to be squashed.
No wonder he ran away.
Now then, for Squad 7's next mission,
we have several available tasks.
Huh?
Among them babysitting the chief
counselor's three-year-old, helping his
wife to do the shopping,
digging up potatoes... No!
I want to go on a real mission!
Something challenging and exciting,
not this little kid stuff.
Come on, old man!
He's got a point.
But he's such a pain.
I knew this was coming.
How dare you!
You're just a brand new Ganeem with no
experience!
Like everyone else, you
start with simple missions
to develop your skills
and prove yourself!
Are you serious?
Babysitting is not a mission!
It's just a stupid...
Will you put a lid on it?
Naruto!
It seems you do not understand the tasks
you have been given.
Listen.
Many different kinds of requests come into
our village every day.
From babysitting to assassination.
These requests are carefully recorded,
analyzed, then ranked A, B, C,
or D, depending on their difficulty.
We ninja are also ranked by ability.
Hokage at the top, Shounin, Shunin,
and Ganeem at the bottom.
At the highest level, we
select the missions and assign
them to ninja who have the
appropriate skill and experience.
If mission is successful, we receive a fee
that supports our village and our work.
If Indo-®T Ведьmo complex are exercises
just started which believe that at the
Comics Sonic eases can do that mock thing
every 2 minutes there or MRI pressure this
VI in the background J T The first thing
we can do is coming back, but that would
require exactly 6 hours, which are meant
to go for this video.
So I had this Tonkatsu
Ramen yesterday and
that I'm thinking of miso
ramen today- Silence!
Oh, sorry.
AH!
You always lecture me like you're my
Grandfather!
I'm not the little brat who used to pull
pranks all the time!
I'm a ninja now, and I want a ninja
mission!
I'm going to hear about this later.
So be it.
Since you are so determined, I'm going to
give you a C-ranked mission.
You'll be bodyguards on a journey.
Really?
Yes!
Who?
Are we guarding a princess?
Or some bigwig counselor?
Don't be so impatient.
I will bring him in now.
Send in our visitor.
What the?
A bunch of little snot-nosed kids?
And you, a little one with the idiotic
look on your face.
You really expect me to believe you're a
ninja?
Who's the little one with the idiotic look
on his...
I'll demolish you!
Let me get my hands off of you!
You can't demolish the client,
Naruto.
It doesn't work that way.
I am Tazuna, a master bridge-builder.
And I must return to my kingdom.
Country, I'm building a bridge there that
will change our world.
And I expect you to get me there safely,
even if it means giving up your life.
Yeah!
All right!
What are you getting so excited about,
Naruto?
This is the first time I ever left the
village!
I'm a traveler now, believe it!
Hey!
Am I supposed to trust my life to this
runt?
He's a joke!
He's with me, and I'm a Jonin,
so you don't need to worry.
This runt, he's a joke!
Hey!
Never insult a ninja!
It's a big mistake!
And I'm one of the greatest ninja ever!
Someday, I'm gonna be a Hokage,
and you'll look up to me!
My name's Naruto Uzumaki!
Remember it!
Hokage are powerful and wise.
You are puny and brainless.
The day you become Hokage, I'll sprout
wings and fly.
Ah!
Shut up!
I'm willing to do anything to become
Hokage, no matter what it takes!
And when I do, everyone will have to admit
that I'm the top ninja, including you!
You can become Hokage ten times over,
and to me, you'll still be nobody.
A loser.
I'm gonna make you pay for that right now!
I told you, you're supposed to protect the
client, not attack him.
Let me go!
I'll show you!
That's right!
I'm talking to you!
Say, Mr. Tazuna...
What is it?
Your country is the Land of Waves,
right?
Yeah?
What of it?
Kakashi-sensei, there are ninja in that
country too, aren't there?
No.
There are no ninja in the Land of Waves.
But in other countries, there
are hidden villages, each with
their own different customs
and cultures, where ninja reside.
To the people of this continent, the
existence of shinobi villages means strength.
Military strength.
In other words, that's how
they protect themselves and
maintain the balance of power
with neighboring countries.
The ninja villages are not controlled by
any government.
They're independent and have equal status.
Now, a small island like the Land of Waves
has natural protection from the sea,
so there's no need for a ninja village.
And it has very little power, but it's a
long way off to do what kujisnyevas
excited me the five ancient lands that
possess shinobi villages are of the Land
of Fire, Water, Lightning, Wind,
and Earth.
They each occupy vast territories.
And together, they are known as the five
great shinobi nations.
The land of fire has the village hidden in
the leaves.
The land of water, the village hidden in
the mist.
The land of lightning, the village hidden
in the clouds.
The land of wind, the village hidden in
the sand.
And the land of earth, the village hidden
in the stones.
Only the leaders of
these hidden villages are
permitted the name
Kage, which means shadow.
Well, anyway, there are no ninja battles
in a C-ranked mission, so you can relax.
Then we're not going to run into any
foreign enemy ninja or anything like that.
Not likely.
What?
Do it!
Kakashi sensei!
Huh?
I can't get loose.
I've got to stop them, I've got to stop
them!
Huh?
Stop them!
Stay behind me!
Ah!
Hi.
Kakashi sensei!
He's alive!
Huh.
Show off.
Huh?
But he was... what?
Naruto, sorry I didn't help you right
away.
I didn't mean for you to get hurt.
I just didn't think you'd freeze up like
that.
Good job, Sasuke.
Very smooth.
You too, Sakura.
I was useless!
And Sasuke was so cool!
Like he'd done this a thousand times!
Didn't he feel scared at all?
He looked so calm, not a scratch on him!
And I was so lame!
He had to come up and save me!
Ugh!
Why can't I keep up with them?
Hey.
Yeah?
You're not hurt, are ya?
Scaredy cat.
Sasuke!
Naruto!
Stand still.
These ninja have poison in their claws.
We need to take it out of you quickly.
You have to open the wound and remove it.
It's in your blood, so don't move around.
That spreads the poison.
By the way,
Mr. Tazuna... Yeah, what?
We need to talk.
They're Chunin from the village hidden in
the mist.
Their specialty is relentless attack.
They keep fighting no matter what the
sacrifice.
How did you know about our ambush?
A puddle.
On a clear day, when it hasn't rained in
weeks.
In that case, why'd you leave it for the
Ganin to do the fighting?
I could have taken them out quickly,
but then I'd have learned nothing.
I had to know who their target was.
And what they were after.
Hm?
What are you getting at?
This.
I wanted to know if they were after us.
Ninja attacking ninja.
Or if they were after you, the master
bridge builder.
When you put in your
request, you asked for
standard protection from
robbers and highwaymen.
You didn't say there were ninja looking
for you, hunting you down.
Our task was simply to get
you to your destination and
protect you while you
finished building your bridge.
If we knew we'd be fielding attacks from
enemy ninja, we would have staffed
differently and charged for the cost of a
bee mission.
Apparently, you have your reasons,
but lying to us is not acceptable.
We are now beyond the scope of this
mission.
We're Ganin.
This is too advanced for our level of
training.
We should go back.
And I really think we
need to treat Naruto's
wound and get the poison
out as soon as possible.
Huh?
Naruto's hand could become a problem.
I guess we should go back to the village.
Why am I so different?
Why am I always...
Naruto!
Stop that!
What are you doing?
I worked so hard to get here!
Pushing myself until it hurt!
Training alone for hours!
Anything to get stronger!
To reach my dream!
I will never back down again!
And let someone else rescue me!
I will never run away!
And I will not lose to Sasuke!
Upon this wound, I make this pledge.
Believe it!
Bridge Builder, I'll complete this mission
and protect you with this kunai knife!
Don't worry, I'll be fine!
Naruto, uh, that was really cool how you
took the poison out and all.
But if you lose any more blood,
you're going to die.
Good idea to stop the bleeding now.
Seriously.
No!
I'm too young for it to all end like this!
Show me your hand!
No!
Help!
Naruto!
You've got a self-abusive personality!
It's called masochism!
The wound... it's already starting to
heal.
You failed.
You failed?!
What is this, amateur knight?
I put out big money for you!
I thought you were supposed to be hotshot
assassins!
Stop whining.
This time, I'll go personally.
And this sword will be the last thing he
ever sees.
You sure about that?
Apparently, Tatsuna has a high-level ninja
guarding him.
And since your first attempt failed,
they'll be expecting you back.
They'll be waiting, watching.
It'll take someone with very advanced
skills!
Who do you think you're dealing with?
The Demon of the Hidden Mist.
This fog's so thick.
You can't see anything.
The bridge isn't far now.
Our destination's just ahead.
The Land of Waves.
It's huge!
What?
Quiet!
I told you, no noise!
Why do you think we're traveling like
this, huh?
Cutting off the engine and rowing?
Moving through the dense fog, so they
don't see us?
Mr. Tatsuna...
Before we reach the pier, I want to ask
you something.
The men who are after you... I need to
know why.
If you don't tell us...
I'm afraid I'll have to end this mission
when we drop you ashore.
I have no choice but to tell you.
No.
I want you to know the truth.
Like you said, this is beyond the scope of
the original mission.
The one who seeks
my life is a very short
man who casts a very
long and deadly shadow.
But who is it?
You know him.
At least I'm sure you've heard his name
before.
He's one of the wealthiest men in the
world.
The shipping magnate, Gato.
Huh?
Gato?
Of Gato Transport?
He's a business leader.
Everyone knows him.
He's a very powerful tycoon from a famous
company, that's true.
But below the surface, with the same
ruthless methods he uses to take over
businesses and nations, he sells drugs and
contraband.
Using gangs and ninja.
It was one year ago, when Gato first set
his sight on the land of waves.
He came to our island
and used his vast wealth to
take total control of our
transport and shipping.
Anyone who tried to stand in his way
simply... disappeared.
In an island nation.
A man who controls the sea controls
everything.
Finance, government, our very lives.
But there's one thing he fears.
The bridge.
When it is complete, it will join us to
the land and that will break his control.
I don't understand.
If you knew he was
dangerous, knew he'd send ninja
to eliminate you, why
did you hide that from us?
Because the land of waves...
is a small, impoverished nation.
Even our nobles have little money.
They can't pay for an A or B ranked
mission.
It's too expensive.
If you end the mission when you drop me
ashore...
there will be no bridge.
They'll assassinate me before I reach
home.
But... don't feel bad about that.
Of course my sweet little
grandson will be able to... be upset.
He'll cry...
Granddad!
I want my granddad!
Oh.
And my daughter will condemn the ninja of
the Hidden Leaves...
denouncing and blaming you for abandoning
her father and living her life in sorrow.
Well...
I guess we have no other choice.
We'll have to keep guarding you.
I win.
We're approaching the shore.
Tazuna.
We've been very fortunate.
No one has noticed us so far.
Nice going.
Yeah!
That's as far as I go.
Good luck.
Right.
Thank you for taking such a risk.
Just be careful.
Okay.
Take me to my home.
And I mean get me there in one piece.
Right.
I'll be there in a minute.
The next ninja they send won't be Chunin.
They'll be Jonin.
Elite ninja with deadly skills.
I'm not letting Sasuke get all the glory
this time.
Believe it.
Over there!
It was just a mouse.
Mouse?
Yeah, right.
Everyone can see through your stupid act.
You're so obvious it's embarrassing.
Naruto.
Those are kunai knives.
They're dangerous.
Stop trying to scare me, you scruffy
little dwarf!
Hey.
Is someone hiding over there?
No.
They're over there.
That's it, Naruto.
What?
Why'd you do that?
Someone really is following us.
I mean it.
Yeah, right.
Quit lying and acting like a dumb kid.
Oh, I'm out of here.
Naruto!
Look what you did!
A... A rabbit!
Sorry, little rabbit.
I'm sorry.
Now this fuss over our rodent.
That's a snow rabbit.
But the color... They only
have white fur during winter.
When the days are short and there's little
sunlight.
This rabbit was raised
indoors, away from the
light, which could only
be for one purpose.
Hmm.
No wonder the Demon Brothers failed in
their mission.
It's the copy ninja from the village
hidden in the leaves.
Kakashi of the Sharingan.
That must be...
I'm ready this time.
I'm not gonna lose out to Sasuke!
Well, well, if it isn't
Zabuza Momochi, rogue
ninja from the village
hidden in the mist.
Ready?
Go!
Get back.
He's not like those other ninja.
He's in a whole other league.
If he's our opponent...
This could be treacherous.
Kakashi of the Sharingan Eye.
Did I get that right?
It's too bad, huh?
But you'll have to hand over the old man.
Sharingan, what is that?
Now quick!
Manji formation!
Protect the bridge builder and stay out of
this fight.
I taught you teamwork.
Now it's time to use it.
I'm ready.
His eye!
What is that?
Well, looks like I get to see the
Sharingan in action.
This is an honor.
Everyone keeps saying, Sharingan,
Sharingan.
Will someone please tell me what Sharingan
is?
Sharingan.
A rare power.
It resides in the eyes.
The Sharingan is a special, rare form of
doujutsu.
However, there's more to the Sharingan
than that.
A lot more.
You got it right, boy.
But you only scratched the surface.
As for you, Jonin.
In the assassination
unit of the Hidden Mist,
we had a standing order
to destroy you on sight.
Your profile was in our bingo book.
It called you the man who copied over a
thousand jutsu.
Kakashi, the Copy Ninja.
What?
Is Kakashi-sensei such a famous ninja?
Wow!
That's so cool!
The Sharingan is a rare trait that only
occurs in a few members of the Uchiha clan.
My clan.
Could he be...
Enough talking.
I need to exterminate the old man.
Now.
So, I'll have to eliminate you first,
eh, Kakashi?
So be it.
I'll have to eliminate you first,
eh, Kakashi?
He's over there!
Standing on the water!
He's building up a huge amount of chakra.
Ninja Arch, Hidden Mist Jutsu!
He vanished!
He'll come after me first.
But... who is he?
Zabuza Momochi.
The ex-leader of the Hidden Mist
Association.
He's a master of the Silent Killing
Technique.
So don't lower your guard.
The
mist is getting thicker and thicker!
The Land of Waves is surrounded by ocean.
The swirling mists are ever-present.
Sensei!
Eight points.
What's that?
Larynx... spine... lungs... liver...
jugular... subclavian artery... kidneys...
heart... Now... which
will be my kill point?
What an intense thirst for blood.
One shallow breath...
One tiny movement of the eye is enough to
bring on instant death.
No.
I can't bear it.
I'd rather take my own life.
Sasuke!
Calm down.
I'll protect you with my life.
All of you.
I will not allow my comrades to die.
Trust me.
I wouldn't be so sure.
It's over.
Look!
Sensei!
Behind you!
Die!
The Water Clone, Jutsu.
It can't be...
Don't move.
Now it's over.
All right!
You really don't get it, do you?
Your technique is nothing but a crass
imitation.
I'll never be defeated by a mere copycat
ninja like you.
You are full of surprises, though.
You'd already copied my Water Clone,
Jutsu, when you made your little speech.
You can't be so sure.
I'll protect you with my life.
All of you.
Very skillfully executed.
You made your clone say
those words to draw my attention
while you hid in the mist,
waiting for me to make my move.
Nice try.
I'm not that easy to fool.
Now.
Makibishi spikes.
Trying to slow me down.
Foolish.
This isn't normal water.
It's dense.
Heavy.
Fool.
Water prison jutsu!
No!
Escaping into the water?
Bad mistake.
This prison is made of water, but it's
stronger than steel.
I'll finish you off later.
But first, your little friends will have
to be eliminated.
Water clone jutsu!
He's even more skilled than I thought.
You think wearing a headband makes you a
ninja?
When you've hovered between life and death
so many times it doesn't faze you,
then you may be called a ninja.
When you've become so
deadly your profile is entered in
my bingo book, then you
may have earned the title ninja.
But to call upstarts like you ninja is a
jerk.
He disappeared again!
You're just brats.
Naruto!
Listen!
Get the bridge builder and run!
You can't win this fight!
He's using all his power
to keep me in this prison,
so he can only fight
you with his water clone.
But the clone can't go far from his real
body.
If you get away from him, he can't follow.
Now run!
Sasuke, no!
He got Sasuke!
So this is what a Jonin is.
A true elite ninja.
Seriously!
He'll annihilate me!
Now I saw how命 come over here for a
minute.
I've got something special I want to give
you.
Congratulations.
You graduate.
That's what happens.
An enemy takes a hostage and you have an
impossible choice.
On every mission, your life is on the
line.
You pass.
I'm not the little brat who used to pull
pranks all the time!
I'm a ninja now and I want a ninja
mission!
To be the greatest Hokage!
Then the whole village
will stop disrespecting
me and start treating
me like I'm somebody!
Somebody important!
That's right.
I'm a ninja now.
Believe it!
I swore an oath of pain!
I won't run away!
Fool.
What are you thinking, charging at him by
yourself?
Even Sasuke couldn't get to him!
We're only Ganine.
We can't defeat a Jonine.
What did you think you'd accomplish by
that?
The headband?
That's what he wanted?
Hey, you.
The freak with no eyebrows.
Put this in your bingo book.
The ninja that will become Hokage of the
village, hidden in the leaves.
He never backs down.
His name's Naruto Uzumaki.
I thought he was all talk, but this kid's
got guts.
All right, Sasuke.
Listen up.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
I've got a plan.
So you're finally thinking about teamwork,
huh?
Why do I have this feeling?
Naruto's so... determined.
All right.
Now, guys, let's go wild!
Big words for such a little man.
You think your plan's going to keep you in
the game?
This isn't good.
What are you doing?
I told you to run!
This fight was over the moment I got
caught!
Now take off!
Your mission is not to prove how brave you
are!
It's to save the Bridge Builder!
Stay on mission!
Bridge Builder?
Well, I... I guess this all happened
because of me.
Because of my desire to live.
But I won't let that stand in your way
now.
Forget about me and do what you have to
do!
Go ahead and fight to save your sensei!
All right.
You hear that?
Yeah, believe it.
You ready?
You really haven't learned anything,
have you?
Still playing your little game,
pretending to be ninja?
When I was your age, this hand had already
crushed many opponents.
Zabuza, the demon.
Oh, so I was in your book too,
huh?
Long ago, in the village hidden in the
mist, also known as Blood Mist Village,
before a student could become a ninja,
there was one final test.
Do you know about the graduation exam?
What graduation exam?
What's the big deal, anyway?
We had graduation tests too!
Did you have to kill the other students to
pass?
Huh?
Imagine young ninja
like you, eating together,
training together, and
then comes the final exam.
Only they change the rules.
Kill or be killed.
You can't stop while your opponent still
breathes.
He was your friend, shared your dreams.
Now it's him or you.
That's so cruel!
Ten years ago, in the village hidden in
the mist, the graduation exam changed.
One year before, a dark evil had filled
the school with terror.
What evil?
What kind of change?
What caused the terror?
Without pause or hesitation, a young boy
who was not even a ninja approached the
class and took down over a hundred other
students.
Oh!
It... it felt so... good.
Sasuke!
You're nothing.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Oh, Shadow Clones.
And there's quite a few of them.
Here we go!
His
skills are too advanced.
I'm not giving up!
I've still got this!
Sasuke!
So that was your plan.
Not bad, Naruto.
You got me.
Demon Wind Shuriken!
A shuriken?
He'll never touch me with that.
Oh, that hurts!
Ooh!
I passed the clone and
aimed for my real body... smart.
Smart... but not smart enough.
A second shuriken in the shadow of the
first.
I told you a shuriken can't touch me.
What?
Eat this!
I'll destroy you!
Kakashi-sensei!
Naruto, that was an excellent plan.
You've really grown, haven't you?
I knew I couldn't beat him with my shadow
clones.
That was just to distract him.
Well, he fought the clones I turned into
the demon when shuriken.
He didn't know what to do, believe it!
Don't brag, you just lucked out.
The whole thing was just a fluke!
You can call it a fluke, but their
teamwork was flawless.
They knew what to do without even talking
about it.
Most of the time they act like they hate
each other, and yet they're a perfect team.
I got distracted and lost my grip on the
water prison.
Don't flatter yourself.
You weren't distracted, you were forced to
let go.
Your technique worked on me once,
but it won't work again.
So, what's it gonna be?
Ok,
I think I'm gonna get the dagger in order
to forgive from Dmayın...
You don't want it from me?
No, I'm trying!
Still no one actually appeared,
Dabi.
We all should be in the same boat wait
until the amazement is over.
Oh, so many hand signs and he mirrored
them all perfectly... instantly.
Something isn't right.
Two sewer cards simultaneously.
Could he... My movements...
It's as if... it's as if he knows what I'm
going to do next.
What?
Is he reading my mind as well?
He looks at me with that eye.
It makes you furious, doesn't it?
All you're doing is copying me.
Like a monkey.
You can't beat me with cheap tricks.
I'll crush you!
When I finish with you, you'll never open
that monkey mouth again!
What is that?
It's me.
But how?
Is it his illusion jutsu?
Water style.
Giant vortex jutsu.
What?
I was just about to create a vortex,
but he created one first!
He copies my jutsu before I can even do
it!
I can't keep up!
You're finished.
How?
Can you... see into the future?
Yes.
This is your last battle... ever.
Ever-ever.
You were right.
It was his last battle.
No vital signs.
Thank you.
I've been tracking
Zabuza for a long time,
waiting for this chance
to finally take him down.
By your mask, I see that you're a tracker
ninja from the village hidden in the mist.
Impressive.
You're well informed.
From his size and voice, he must be the
same age as Naruto.
Yet he's an elite assassin.
He's no ordinary kid.
But what is he?
What is this?
Who do you think you are?
Huh?
Did you hear me?
Easy Naruto.
He's not our enemy.
Huh, that's not the point.
Did you see what he did just like that?
Zabuza was huge and powerful like some
kind of monster.
And this kid who's no bigger than me.
He brought down Zabuza with one move like
it was nothing.
How can I accept that?
Well, even if you don't accept it.
Still, it did happen, Naruto.
In this world, there are kids who are
younger than you.
And yet, stronger than me.
Your struggle is over for now.
I must deal with the remains.
There are many secrets in this body.
They must not be allowed to get into the
wrong hands.
Please excuse me.
Farewell.
He disappeared!
We haven't completed the mission yet.
We haven't completed our mission yet.
We still have to get the bridge builder to
his bridge.
Sorry I caused all this trouble for you.
But you can rest in my house when we get
to the village.
All right.
Let's get a move on.
What?
What happened?
Kakashi-sensei!
I think I overdid it with my Sharingan.
Waking up, huh?
Are you all right?
I've been better.
It'll be a week before I can move
normally.
See?
It's better if you don't move.
So just lie down.
Right.
Look, the sensei is coming around!
Listen, sensei.
Your Sharingan is amazing and everything.
But if it puts that much strain on you,
maybe it's not worth it.
Sorry.
Well, he did take down
one of the most powerful
ninja assassins, so
we'll be safe for a while.
Right, but... you know that boy with the
mask?
What about him?
He's from the elite tracking unit of the
village hidden in the mist.
Those masks are only worn by the most
elite shinobi.
What exactly do they do?
The Anbu Black Ops,
also known as the Inferno
Squad, destroy all traces
of a rogue ninja's corpse.
The shinobi's body contains
many secrets, ninjutsu,
chakra, special medicines
used on his body.
These are the secrets of his village.
If his enemies find them, his people will
be in grave danger.
For instance, if I were
to die at the hands of
an enemy, he would try
to analyze my Sharingan.
In the worst case, my entire jutsu could be
stolen and used against our home village.
It is the sacred duty of
the shinobi trackers to
prevent this, to keep
the village's secrets safe.
If a ninja betrays his village,
the trackers hunt him down, eliminate him,
and obliterate every trace of his
existence.
That's their specialty.
What is this?
Something's wrong.
It's like I missed something.
Hey, are you okay?
Sensei?
Tracker ninja deal with
the body immediately,
on the spot, so there's
no room for error.
Is that really important?
Think about it.
Do you remember what that tracker did with
Zabuza's body?
We don't know what he did.
I mean, I guess he took it away somewhere.
Exactly.
But why?
He should have worked on Zabuza right
there, as quickly as possible.
Think of the weapons he used for the
takedown.
Do you remember what they were?
Throwing needles.
No way.
Exactly.
None of it adds up.
Huh.
What are you all yammering about?
You demolished that assassin.
Here's the truth.
Zabuza's still alive.
But we saw his body!
Believe it!
Kakashi-sensei, you checked him yourself!
You said that his heart stopped!
His heart did stop.
But... that was just a temporary state,
to simulate death.
The weapons that tracker used are called
senbon.
They can pierce deeply, but rarely kill
unless they hit a vital organ.
Not in the neck.
They're modified from needles used for
medical treatments, like acupuncture.
Trackers are trained to know every detail
of the human body.
Causing the heart to
stop temporarily while
keeping the body alive
is an easy matter for them.
First, he carried Zabuza's body away,
even though it's much heavier than he is.
Second, he used senbon, which have a
precise effect, but are rarely fatal.
From these two factors, we can conclude
that the tracker is still alive.
The tracker wasn't trying to destroy
Zabuza.
He was trying to save him.
Come on, you're overthinking this,
aren't you?
Encountering suspicion, the ninja prepares
quickly.
Hesitation leads to disaster.
Every shinobi knows this saying.
He's actually pleased to hear Zabuza's
alive.
Now Naruto's got another shot at him.
Sensei, you said prepare quickly.
But how can we do that when you can barely
move?
I can still train you.
Hold on!
A little last-minute training won't make
us strong enough to fight Zabuza!
You could barely defeat him, even with
your Sharingan!
We have to be reasonable about this!
What, are you trying to get us killed?
Sakura, why was I able to stop Zabuza?
Because you all helped me.
You've grown.
Naruto.
Huh?
You've grown the most.
So you noticed, Kakashi-sensei!
Now things are going to get better,
believe it!
I don't believe it, and nothing's going to
be good!
Who are you?
Inari, where have you been?
Welcome back, Grandpa!
Inari, that was very rude.
These ninja helped your Grandpa and
brought him here safely.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm rude to them, too.
Mom, don't you see?
These people are going to die!
Gato and his men will come back and find
them and wipe them out!
What did you say, brat?
Listen up!
You know what a super ninja is?
Well, that's me, only a lot better!
I'm going to be Hokage!
This Gato or Blotto or whatever he's
called is no match for a real hero like me!
Huh, there's no such thing as a hero.
You're just full of stupid ideas!
What'd you say?
Naruto, calm down!
If you want to stay alive, you should go
back where you came from.
Inari, wait, where are you going?
To look out at the ocean.
I want to be alone.
Sorry about that.
Who does that brat think he is?
I'm going to put him in his place right
now!
Huh?
He's crying?
No, Daddy, no!
All right, training starts now.
Right!
First, we will begin with a review of
Chakra, the ninja.
Chakra is a ninja's basic source of power.
Understanding Chakra is essential.
We know that.
He's right.
A long time ago, we learned about,
uh, Catra.
Chakra?
Go ahead, Sakura.
All right, Naruto.
Chakra is the elemental life energy a
ninja uses in Jutsu.
It's the source of all his power.
Now, this energy has two forms.
Physical energy, which
exists in all the cells
in the entire body,
all working together.
And, spiritual energy,
the primal source of power
which is intensified through
training and experience.
As you see, these two types
of Chakra must be drawn
out and brought together
in order to perform Jutsu.
Notice the interplay between physical and
spiritual power.
That's the key.
Finally, hand signs.
Focus and unleash the Chakra.
Right on all points.
Iruka-sensei really did have some
excellent students.
Huh!
What's the big deal with all these
complicated explanations?
The whole point is to learn the Jutsu,
isn't it?
Naruto's right for once.
We're already using Chakra energy in our
Jutsu.
No.
You have not mastered this power.
You've barely scratched the surface of it.
What do you mean?
Calm down and listen.
It's just like Sakura said.
You have to draw on
physical and spiritual
energies and then combine
them within yourself.
But, how do you do that?
Each Jutsu requires different types of
Chakra in different proportions.
You must select and combine them in
exactly the right way.
Up to now, you've just guessed at the
proportions, hoping they'd come out right.
Even if you produce a
lot of Chakra, unless you
can balance and control
it, it's all worthless.
The Jutsu won't work at all, or it'll just
be a joke.
You waste so much energy that way.
Then you're out of Chakra and you can't
fight at all.
You're just a target.
Uh, so how do we change that?
Train so hard that controlling your Chakra
becomes second nature.
To achieve this goal, you must be ready to
put your life on the line.
What do we have to do?
Climb a tree.
Climb a tree?
That's right.
But there's just one rule.
No hands.
What?
You're kidding.
Am I?
Let's see.
He's climbing!
Straight up!
And he's only using his feet!
Well, you get the idea.
Focus the Chakra toward the soles of your
feet and use it to connect to the tree.
This is one way to apply the power of
Chakra.
Wait a minute!
That's a nice trick, but how does it help
us fight Zabuza?
It's the only way to fight him,
Sakura.
That's the entire goal of this training.
First, you'll learn to
draw a precise amount
of Chakra to a precise
point in your body.
This is difficult even for advanced ninja.
This type of climbing requires a subtle
mix of physical and spiritual energy.
And the bottoms of the feet are the most
difficult points to focus Chakra.
Are you getting the picture?
If you can master this, you'll be able to
master any Jutsu.
Well, theoretically.
The second point is to learn to maintain
your Chakra levels.
When a ninja is focused
in battle, it's even
harder to control and
maintain his Chakra levels.
A deadly mistake.
To avoid this, maintaining Chakra must
become second nature, effortless.
Well, I can talk about this all day, but
that won't advance your skills, will it?
You need to apply the power of Chakra
through training.
Use the kunai knife to
mark the tree at the highest
point you can climb
without using your hands.
Then try to get past that mark the next
time and the next.
At first, you'll need
to run at the tree so
your momentum can take
you as high as possible.
Until you get used to it.
I'm more than ready!
This is gonna be no sweat all the way!
Believe it!
Remember what you said, Sensei!
I'm the one who's grown the most!
You're definitely the one who talks the
most.
Now get focused and do it!
Well, he did say that.
Okay.
First, I need to draw the Chakra to the
bottom of my feet.
Okay.
First, I need to draw the Chakra to the
bottom of my feet.
I got it!
Charge!
This is harder than I thought.
The balance has to be perfect.
If the Chakra's too strong, it smashes the
tree and pushes you off.
But if it's not strong enough...
You just tumble back down.
Like Naruto.
That's about what I expected from Sasuke.
And Naruto.
Hey, this is fun!
Sakura!
Yeah!
Way to go, Sakura!
I always knew you were awesome!
Believe it!
It does sort of tick me off, though.
Whatever.
I thought Sasuke would be impressed.
Now he's mad at me.
Why is it always like that?
Well, not only does
Sakura understand Chakra,
she can control and
maintain it as well.
We spoke about someone becoming Hokage one
day, didn't we?
Seems Sakura's got the best chance of
that, wouldn't you say?
And as for the great Uchiha clan,
maybe they're not so great after all.
Shut up, Sensei!
You talk too much!
Sasuke's gonna hate me now!
All right.
I think they're motivated.
Of course, Naruto and Sasuke both have far
more Chakra within.
If this training works, their mastery of
Chakra will become a valuable asset.
All right!
First I'll match Sasuke!
Then I'm going all the way to the top!
Believe it!
Huh.
What a waste of time.
They don't know what they're up against.
Hmm.
I'm totally worn out.
How can they just keep going like that?
Ow!
Hah!
Naruto isn't making any progress at all.
Knowing him, any minute now he'll give up
and throw a tantrum.
Ah!
There he goes.
He's so predictable, it's embarrassing.
Hmm?
Uh, uh... Hey, you're good at this.
How about some advice?
Uh... But please don't
tell Sasuke I asked.
Please, please!
He's catching on.
From now on, he'll get stronger and
stronger.
Stronger?
How strong?
After all, Naruto possesses more Chakra
than Sasuke.
In fact, the amount of Chakra he possesses
is greater than my own.
You always this lazy?
Where's that weird blonde kid and the one
with the attitude?
They're training, climbing trees.
Too tough for you?
No, in fact, I'm the best.
That's why the sensei sent me here to
guard you.
You're joking.
Waaaaah!
Tatsuno, uh, I need to talk to you.
Huh?
What about?
Uh, thing is, I've been thinking a lot
about the bridge.
And I decided... I've pushed my luck far
enough.
I want out.
Now you're going to quit on me just like
that?
You're kidding!
You know, I stayed on because of our
friendship.
But I'm putting my life on the line every
day I stay here.
Gato and his thugs will show up
eventually.
When they do, they'll kill you and the
bridge will never get finished anyway.
It's a lost cause, Tazuna.
Why don't we stop now while we can still
get out of this alive?
This is our bridge.
Our island is poor.
And it will stay that way until this
bridge connects us to the mainland.
Commerce, trade, and hope.
That's what we're building here.
There's not gonna be much hope if we're
all dead.
It's already noon.
Let's break for lunch.
Tazuna, let's not end it like this.
Save your breath.
Oh, and Giichi, don't bother coming back
after lunch.
Why is it so hard?!
I'm not gonna lose out to you!
Sorya!
Um,
where are we going?
You wanna eat tonight, don't ya?
I gotta pick up some things for dinner.
Thief!
What's wrong with these people?
Here we are.
Welcome.
This is a store?
There's nothing here.
You pervert!
Wow, you really surprised me back there.
Girls around here don't fight like that.
They should.
Something's seriously wrong here.
Again?
Hey, buster!
Uh... Uh...
Uh... Please?
Hmm...
Uh...
Here.
Oh, thank you!
Hmph.
This is how it's been since Gato came
here.
The children suffer, and the adults are
afraid to stand up to him.
They've lost all hope.
That's why we have to finish the bridge.
It will bring commerce and trade.
But much more importantly, that bridge is
a symbol of courage.
We must restore the spirit of our people.
When the bridge is finished, people will
start to believe again.
They'll believe that they can live with
dignity.
We can't let Gato stop us.
He's still climbing!
That's impossible!
Damn!
He's catching up to me inch by inch!
No, no, no!
If I think about Sasuke, I'll lose my
concentration!
Believe it!
Come on, Naruto.
Relax.
Focus on the tree.
Yeah!
I can feel it!
I'm going all the way this time!
Hey, Naruto!
Sasuke!
What are you doing?
I was trying to focus my chakra!
Well, uh, you know, the thing is...
The thing is what?
You, you know, you asked Sakura for advice
when she was here.
So what did she tell you?
I'm not telling you.
This is fantastic!
It's been ages since we've had so many
guests around our table.
I want some more!
Don't eat so much or you're going to puke
it up!
I have to eat.
And I have to eat more than him.
It's the only possible way I'll get strong
enough to beat him.
That's true, but puking won't help you.
Excuse me, this picture is torn.
Is there some reason for that?
It's my husband.
They used to call him a hero in this land.
Father, you can't talk about him like that
in front of Inari, you know that!
Inari, so... I mean, what happened to him?
Is there a story behind this?
He wasn't his real father.
He came into our family later.
And he brought so much happiness.
He and Inari were very close.
In those days...
Inari used to laugh all the time.
But then...
All that ended.
He never laughs or smiles anymore.
Ever since the day everything changed.
Poochie!
Poochie, no!
That's not his name.
Starting today, his name is Shooting Star.
And he's my dog now!
No, he's not!
He's my dog!
And his name's not Shooting Star!
I've had him since he was a puppy!
He's my friend and he doesn't belong to
you!
Just shut up!
Poochie!
See what happens when you don't listen to
me?
Now I'm not going to lift a finger to help
him.
Okay, you can let him go.
Why did you do that?
My dog is going to drown!
Ha!
If he's your dog, then jump in and get
him!
Be a big hero and save your friend!
After all that big talk, you're not going
to let him go under, are you?
You won't even help his precious little
Poochie!
I... I can't swim!
And I'm scared!
I'm sorry, Poochie.
Hey, you made such a big deal about him,
go get him!
I think you went too far, Akane.
I mean, he could really drown or
something.
Help!
Please!
Forget about it.
I don't know.
You say one more word and you're going in
next!
Got it?
I don't want to die!
Pooch!
He's shooting stars running away!
Get him!
Oh no... I can't breathe... I...
I can't breathe... I can't
breathe... Waking up, huh?
Finally!
I had a little talk with those kids.
They won't bother you again.
Here, eat.
Am I alive?
Is this for real?
Did you pull me out of the water,
mister?
Have a bite to eat first.
Then we can talk all about it.
I see, your dog abandoned you too,
huh?
In my country, dogs are very loyal.
They stand by their masters.
Then again, you abandoned the dog first,
so what can you expect?
I really wanted to save him, but I just
froze.
I was just so scared.
I guess that I just don't have any
courage.
Hey, come on.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You're a kid.
When I was your age, I was scared too.
It's no big deal.
But always remember this.
Live your life so you have nothing to
regret.
If you care about something, protect it.
No matter how tough, no matter how sad,
you've got to keep trying.
Even if you have to put your life on the
line, protect it with both arms.
Never give in!
We've got trouble, Kaiser!
The floodgate's open and the water's
rising!
If we don't stop, the lower district will
be flooded!
What?
Further!
Inari, get me some rope!
Hurry!
Right!
See where the gate is?
We need to get a line out there to pull it
closed!
A line?
You have to swim out there to do that!
It's impossible!
No one can make it through that current!
If we don't do it, the whole district will
be wiped out!
It's the only way!
I'll do it!
Kaiser!
Don't be foolish!
You'll never make it!
Father!
Don't worry.
Nothing can stop your dad.
This is our village, so we've got to do
everything we can to help.
If you care about something, protect it.
No!
He's gone!
He made it!
He tied the rope on!
Alright!
Let's pull it closed!
Everybody, come on!
From that time on, Kaiser was considered a
hero in this land.
He taught us all the meaning of courage
and Inari was so proud to be his son.
And took over.
He terrorized the whole village.
Only Kaisa stood up to him.
Gato couldn't have a local hero getting in
his way.
It took his whole gang to stop one man.
You overplayed your hand, Kaisa.
All that talk.
About how you're going to protect this
village with your two arms.
Those arms aren't much work now,
are they?
Still got that defiant look in your eye,
though.
Well, my men will get rid of that.
Get to work on him.
Get down there!
Listen up!
This man has defied the Gato Corporation.
He has disturbed the order of the Kaisa.
He is the only survivor of this land.
His punishment is execution.
Let this be an example so no one will dare
stand in our way again.
Father!
Inari, don't!
Do it.
Father, no!
Daddy!
Since then, Inari's changed.
So did Tsunami and all our people.
We lost our will.
What are you doing down there,
Naruto?
You better take the day off.
No more training.
You've used too much chakra.
If you push any harder, it could kill you.
I'm gonna prove it!
Hm?
Prove what?
I'll prove that... that it's true!
That in this world...
...there are real heroes!
TURYA!
Good
morning, everyone!
AAAAAaaghhhhhhh.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
Naruto's not here.
Looks like he was out all night again.
He's gone completely crazy.
He's out climbing trees in the dark.
He could be dead by now.
You know, from using up too much of his
chakra.
Well, I certainly hope he's okay.
A child spending the night in the woods
alone.
There's nothing to worry about.
Naruto's a goofy kid, but he's also a
full-fledged ninja.
He can handle himself.
Sakura's right.
Naruto's such a loser.
He's probably lying out there dead
somewhere.
You'll catch cold if you sleep here.
Wake up.
Who the heck are you?
Oh, uh, uh, I mean... Hi there,
where did you come from?
You know, what are you doing out here and
all that?
I'm gathering herbs.
Herbs?
Yes.
That's right.
They're for treating illnesses and healing
wounds.
You start work early, huh, sis?
I like it early.
It's calm, but I didn't think I'd find
anyone sleeping out here in the woods.
I'm training.
So are you a ninja?
Because I noticed that headband you're
wearing.
Or are you just making a fashion
statement?
You noticed that?
Oh, right.
Only supercoolninja can wear these.
Oh, really?
I see.
That's very impressive.
But... does that mean you're training for
something dangerous?
I'm just developing my skills so I can get
stronger!
You seem very strong now.
Isn't that enough?
No, no, I need to get stronger and
stronger!
I have to keep practicing!
How so?
Why so?
Why is it so important?
So I can become the best ninja in my
village!
Then everyone will know who I am and
they'll all respect me!
There's also a certain person,
a kid, that I have to prove something to!
So are you doing it for this certain
person?
Or are you doing all this training for
yourself?
What are you laughing about?
What's so funny?
Is there someone who's precious to you?
Someone who...
What are you saying, sis?
What do you mean precious?
What's she thinking?
You see, when a person has something
precious that they want to protect,
then they become genuinely strong.
If you ever lay a hand on my sensei...
I'll kill you!
Yeah, I hear ya!
I know exactly what you're saying!
You will get strong.
Very strong.
Goodbye.
We'll meet again sometime.
Oh, by the way... I'm a boy.
No way!
He's prettier than Sakura!
You won't be able to get over me,
Sakuya!
I've had enough, Sakuya!
I've seen a lot of weird things in my life
before, but this one takes the cake!
Ow, hey, what did you do that for?
Hey, Torb.
Cut it out!
Did you just forget about breakfast?
You're such a loser.
Huh?
Hehe... Huh?
Naruto?
Knowing Naruto, he could be anywhere.
And Sasuke hasn't come back either.
I wonder where they are.
Wow!
Naruto can climb that high now using his
chakra?
That's great!
What do you think?
High enough for you guys?
I mean, it's a long way?
Oh, Naruto!
Ah!
Just kidding!
You guys really fell for it!
We were worried about you, Naruto!
I'm gonna strangle you!
You dork!
Why do I think this is going to end badly?
Ugh...
You really are a total loser, Naruto.
Ah!
Sasuke!
Alright, Sasuke!
You're the best!
If I'm still sane by the time I finish
their training, it'll be a miracle.
Hmm.
Naruto Uzumaki, huh?
Huh?
Let's go back!
Alright!
Now they're both late!
I wouldn't have expected that from Sasuke!
What have you been up to?
You look like something the cat dragged
in.
We both made it!
We climbed all the way to the top!
Good.
Now we move on.
Starting tomorrow, you're both bodyguards
for Tazura.
Alright!
You are such a loser!
In a few more days, the bridge will be
finished.
I have you to thank for that.
You've all done great, but you've still
got to be careful.
I've been meaning to ask you this,
but I haven't had the chance until now.
Why did you stay and protect me, even after
you found out I lied to bring you here?
Those who stray from the path of justice
have no courage.
But under the wing of a strong leader,
cowardice cannot survive.
I care.
You're nothing but a coward!
Naruto!
You went too far!
Naruto...
Can I talk to you?
Naruto can be a little harsh sometimes.
But he doesn't hate you.
Your grandfather told us what happened.
To your father.
You probably don't know this, but Naruto
also grew up without a father.
In fact, he never knew either of his
parents.
And he didn't have a single friend in our
village.
Still, I've never seen him cry,
sulk, or give up.
He's always eager to jump in.
He wants to be respected.
That's his dream.
And he'll put his life on the line for
that.
In a heartbeat.
My guess is... he just got tired of crying,
and decided to do something about it.
I think he knows better than any of us
what you're going through.
What Naruto told you earlier?
As cruel as it sounded, he's probably told
himself that a thousand times.
You're recovering quickly.
Just a little longer, Haku.
Yes.
He's sleeping.
What?
The only thing I can
think of is... Yeah, me, too.
So, let's do it.
Let's return.
I'll keep you company.
See you later.
A little pause... and we are back.